Hello friends, welcome to
today's video. In today's video, we are going to
talk about such people.
Today, a very good fall was seen in the stock. So,
we
will discuss these in detail, which will tell you
what is going to happen in this channel in the future.
What should be our plan? If we
already have it in holding, then
how should we manage this stock.
We will discuss these in detail here, we will
discuss technically. So,
you must watch this video carefully
so that all the labels become absolutely
clear to you. And if you like the video, if you like
Nargis, then
like the video. Do subscribe to the channel.
You have
also selected Pocket Oil by pressing this bell icon, so that
you will also keep getting the latest notifications.
Now, if we talk about
such people on flood, then why is there a
fall of more than 4 times in the stock here. At one
time, lovers saw a fall
in the last, if we look here, then from the bottom,
we saw a good recovery here
in the last one hour,
but from the morning  The time is right, if we
look here, we saw a good decline,
which is why
this topic is downward, don't
drink, today you did
not see any chance of fraud anywhere and the stock is almost around
its low level, you have
also closed here, if we
talk about the last five trading sessions, then in the last five
trading systems, you have
not used this not stop much here, it is
trading down around 125%,
but even now if we look, you see
this stock moving down in the last five days,
if we
talk about one month, then in the last one month,
you have made a good return in this
stock, now we are
trading up 125% right now,
but anyway, if we look, then on a monthly
basis also we are
seeing a weak backbone here, if we look here, we
saw a good friend and
after the print, we are seeing a breakdown of the temple run here.
Putli stock on the last one month's time and if we look at it, then here
in one month it has definitely made a positive vitamin A stock,
but here
a sign of reversal is
visible on the basis of one month, if we talk about
six months, then in the last band, you will see that mostly
you will see more on the side, on one
day this straight was done, I had donated blood, that is again
here you are getting the same net reading
and here again you are
getting an indication of a downtrend here
and if we talk here on one year
basis, then the stock is clearly visible on the upside,
from the district level, the stock is clearly visible here in a good downtrend, the
big one is not
seen now, a good downtrend happens,
God, you get a
replacement, from here the stock
starts removing its toe, so
overall if we look at it, then in the friend time
frame, the stock is still
in a negative trend, you will see that the stock has
started trending here  It is in the same but
in the sweater time frame of one month,
you have been given a good return,
you have seen a retracement of the robbers, there
you can again
trigger a selling pressure in the stock here,
so here the first thing is if you want, you can
earn good money by creating a position for the but side for the short term, if you are buying this
stock for investment purpose or you already have the stock in your portfolio,
then you will have to
wait a little more time
here, only after that
you will get good returns, if we
talk here, today mostly all the insurance
sector stocks saw a decline,
if we talk about such
quarters here, let us clear this topic, then it got
listed in 2017, after listing it
gave a good return, approximately it gave you a
return of 30 percent here,
after that a downtrend has already started in the stock,
if we look here on a monthly basis, then let
us  People will
see a trend line backbone forming.
After that, in this topic, you will see a good
downward movement. Here, the stock has a
school bag. Here, you have a downward
moment. Here,
we are seeing a pullback moment. Now,
if this happens at a low, the previous will
operate. You can
see a good movement towards the frozen side here. So,
if we look here,
even in the ministerial time frame, the stock is
visible in the don't friend here only. It is
not in a prank here. Now,
if we talk here on the weekly time frame, then the
attacks are clearly
visible in the time frame. If you look here in the down print, then
one which is above the 3000 level,
you were getting a good support.
Here, you will see that the support was broken.
After breaking this level in the same train, you will see a good
pullback here to the level of Lieutenant. And now,
here again, selling pressure has
started to be triggered. The
image support on the lower side is visible to you.  11:00
line, if the level of Reliance is broken, then
here we
can see a good movement towards trapping us and after that,
all the stocks of 1000 can go here,
so both monthly and sales
time frame, you can see the stock here in the
dot, if we talk
here in Delhi time frame, then
in Delhi time also we can clearly see that the
stock is in a good gauge friend,
here clearly we are getting this
indication, if we talk at the current level, then
after making a good base, a good base was made on 1111 holiday,
now
after giving the record, if you see it clearly here, then
a common pattern has come back and a
lot of message setting has also been seen,
if you look at it again, then in this zone,
even before this, the stock of assistance plus two
and the same level selling pressure has come,
so the selling pressure here can
continue, which will take this stock
towards 1100.  It can take it towards the level, so
in the short term, if you
want to trend here, then you
can create a position here. If you
want to read, then tomorrow if it
crosses below today's music rights, then
you can set a middle east here.
Now, you can keep the stoploss on the upper side, which is
above the high of today's candle,
but if you have kept
this stock in your portfolio for investment
purposes, then you may have to wait here. So,
if you see overall,
in the current time frame, this stock has already given a good
return. Currently, the
stock is in the dot here and right now, till most of the time, you are
seeing a selling pressure in the stock from the upper level.
As long as the frozen level
is intact here, you will not see major selling pressure here.
We can see a good consolidation in this range.
For the period, there can be
a good consolidation between 250 and only after that, there will be
a good upward momentum in the stock.  Side
attacks can be seen, so if
you already have this stock and have purchased only above,
you can hold it here and
see it, you
can also see it by clicking on 10 stoploss because if the level of Tha Hussain is
broken here, then
attacks can be seen again up to 757 here,
so it is better that you
can hold it here right now,
but if you do not have it right now or you have it
and you want to average it, then this is
not the right time to average it, you should not favorite it
until the stock does not fall on 1st April, at least
until it comes into trend on the daily chart,
if you already have it in holding then
you can continue, but no, you do not have to
make a press portion here nor do
you have to average your position here,
so I hope all the things must have become clear to you people, then if you
liked the video then you liked it, then
please like the video and subscribe to the channel
now
Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal Jhal